[音乐]
[Music]
谁是lz司机小子
who the lz driver kid
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
加固先生，你为什么不剪掉小丑
reinforcement sir why don't you cut out the clowning
丽莎，我做了什么，从来没有让我看到你在做我的胜利
lisa what have i done don't ever let me see you doing a victory roll over my
飞机场我再一次以为会击败平民哦，上帝保佑杰米
airfield again i thought it would buck up the civilians oh for god's sake jamie
给你一个机会
give your brain a chance
是的，兄弟，马上去给他们加油，所以无论如何他打了我，让我
go bro refuel them immediately yes sir so anyway he hit me and made me
流鼻血的下士我不是说你的血
nosebleed corporal i don't mean with your blood
我给他们几只袜子，然后重新武装
i'll give them a couple of socks and re-arm them
是的，您好，哈维爵士，巨型飞机在哪里丢失
yes sir hello javi where's jumbo posted missing
昨晚你演的首席执行官哦，是的
last night you acting ceo oh yeah
哪五架可维修飞机中没有备件就没有联系
of what five serviceable aircraft no spares no contact
[音乐]造福于未受过教育的人
[Music] for the benefit of the uneducated among
我们我要翻译阿卡姆不敢相信轿车的堕落
us i shall translate archam can't believe the sedan's fallen
我可以
i can
他们半小时会在这里是没有用的，我们必须立即离开
it's no use they'll be here in half an hour we must leave immediately
是的，让我们摆脱困境，先生，你为什么不跟着我去寻找
yes let's get the hell out of it where to sir why don't you follow me and find
出来吧，白痴，我觉得除非他们之前去过那里
out come on idiot i feel unless they've got there before
我们从这里拿到凉亭，我们去
us get that bowser out of here we'll go
与我们所拥有的
with what we've got
好吧，忘了你的孩子，让我们动起来
all right forget your kid let's move
伟大的得到所有的运输，你可以尝试把男人带出这里
great get all the transport you can try and get the man out of here
所有ncos都立即向我报告[音乐]
all ncos report to me immediately [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
你知道with子鸭怎么办吗
you know what to do with the lame ducks yes sir
[音乐]结束
[Music] over
[音乐]
[Music]
我们没有很长的一天
we haven't got a long day
[音乐]
[Music]
致常任国务卿
to the permanent secretary of state for air
先生，我很荣幸提及最近发生的非常严重的电话
sir i have the honor to refer to the very serious calls which have recently
是在战斗机指挥下做出的，目的是阻止德国人
been made upon fighter command in an attempt to stem the german
我希望并相信我们的军队可能入侵非洲
invasion of the continent i hope and believe that our armies may
在法国和比利时取得胜利，但我们必须
yet be victorious in france and belgium but we have to
面临被击败的可能性
face the possibility that they may be defeated
在这种情况下，我认为没有人会否认英国应该
in this case i presume that there is no one who will deny that england should
即使剩下的
fight on even though the remainder of the
欧洲大陆以德国人为主
continent of europe is dominated by the germans
因此，我必须要求不要再
i must therefore request that not one more
如果本国防卫系统被消耗掉，战斗机将被越过通道
fighter be sent across the channel if the home defense is drained away in
拼命试图纠正法国的局势
desperate attempts to remedy the situation in france
法国失败将涉及最终完成
defeat in france will involve the final complete
和无可挽回的失败，我荣幸地成为
and irremediable defeat of this country i have the honor to be
先生，您一定要服从陶氏马歇尔亲爱的先生
sir your obedience certain h c t dowdy marshall darling sir
我确实意识到怀疑这会把我们摆在哪里
i do realize doubting the position this puts us in
我意识到向法国人许诺了这些中队
i realize that the french have been promised these squadrons
由丘吉尔亲自
by churchill personally
他给了法国总理他的诺言
he's given the french prime minister his word
您确实会怀疑丘吉尔将不得不这样说
you do appreciate doubting that churchill will have to say this
那就是我写它的原因
that's why i wrote it
[音乐]呵呵
[Music] huh
[音乐]
[Music]
哦
oh
这是英国广播公司的家庭服务，这是新闻
this is the bbc home service here is the news
总理丘吉尔今天下午在下议院说
in the house of commons this afternoon the prime minister mr churchill said
维加将军所谓的法国之战结束了
what general vega called the battle of france is over
英国之战即将开始[音乐]
the battle of britain is about to begin [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]外国
[Music] foreign
[音乐]哦
[Music] oh
[音乐]
[Music]
嗯
uh-huh
[音乐]呃
[Music] uh
[音乐]
[Music]
有
there's
[音乐]
[Music]
还有这个房子
and this house
醉
drunk
外国，我要搬家
foreign an i'm gonna move
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
米
m
亲爱的下一位，我很想见你回到瑞士
my dear next i'd love to see you back in switzerland
一小时前，我很快就从柏林来了
so soon i came straight from berlin an hour ago
大使现在会见您，先生，谢谢您。
the ambassador will see you now sir thank you excuse me please
所以大卫再次受命要强调
so david i'm again instructed to emphasize
越狱者希望避免进一步流血
that the fuhrer wishes to avoid further bloodshed
英国不是我们的天敌，他提供保证
england is not our natural enemy and he offers guarantees
如果您在欧洲放手德国，对英国帝国来说
for the british empire if you give germany a free hand in europe
尿液和德国空军想把伦敦弄平
urine and this luftwaffe would like to flatten london
作为入侵的前奏，是不是你要抓住两个肿块
as a prelude to invasion it's two lumps you take isn't it
你们军队剩下的东西在敦刻尔克弃用了武器
what's left of your army abandoned its weapons at dunkirk
你没有防备，只是在玩时间
you're defenseless and just playing for time
我们知道您在华盛顿的举动，我们知道美国人
we know the moves you're making in washington and we know the americans
不会被他们在伦敦的大使馆吸引
won't be drawn in their embassy in london gives you two
周数
weeks
所以什么阻止了你
so what's stopping you
看起来大卫恐惧是很合理的
look david the fear is being very reasonable
他提供的担保经验表明无所畏惧的担保
he offers guarantees experience shows the fearless guarantees guarantee
上次上诉后，丘吉尔没有什么，我们听到了什么
nothing what about churchill after our last appeal what do we hear we
会在沙滩上与他们战斗
will fight them on the beaches with what
温斯顿有时会被液体带走
winston gets carried away sometimes with liquid
勇气让他们清楚地告诉我你不认识他
courage so they tell me clearly you don't know him
大卫，我们对欧洲的要求不高
david we are not asking for anything europe is ours
我们随时可以走进英国
we can walk into britain whenever we like
您认为我们要赌她的希特勒的保证吗？
do you think we're going to gamble on her hitler's guarantees you're making a
那些年来，英国似乎犯了严重的错误
grave mistake all those years in england seem to have
别让你一个聪明人，我们不容易受到惊吓，而且我们
left you none the wiser we're not easily frightened and also we
知道军队越过
know how hard it is for an army to cross the
频道最后一个下士尝试来了
channel last little corporal to try came a
所以不要威胁或命令我们
cropper so don't threaten or dictate to us until
你在白色大厅里游行，即使那样我们也不会听
you're marching up white hall and even then we won't listen
你好
hello
我发脾气是不可原谅的，令人发疯的是他是对的
it's unforgivable i lost my temper the maddening thing is that he's right
他们还没有准备好你就知道你一直在玩
they're not ready you are known you've been playing for time
而且快用完了[音乐]
and it's running out [Music]
傻bit子，他再次给你起名字阿诺德，我花了半个星期让她安顿下来
silly [ __ ] he's calling you names again arnold i spent half a week settling her
和乡下的孩子，现在我很无聊，她说
and the kids in the country and now i'm bored she says
您的精英之一，试图不着陆着陆
one of your elite trying to land without wheels
所以
so
黛西先生，这足以让你
boom sir daisy it's enough to make you
哭泣
weep
[音乐]
[Music]
并欢迎回家，先生的起落架让她有点粘
and welcome home sir undercarriage leave her a bit sticky was
他说是的，事实上
he saying well yes as a matter of fact it was
好吧，我不会告诉公司，先生，如果我是你
well i wouldn't tell the co that sir not if i were you
你可以教猴子飞比
you can teach monkeys to fly better than
那
that
我为那个先生感到非常抱歉，我再也不会留下
i'm terribly sorry about that sir it won't happen again i'd keep your jacket
在男孩身上，你吐了几个小时
on boy how many hours are you done in spits
simon在spitzer 10上打了半个洞
simon on spitzer 10 and a half well make it 11
杰里吃早餐之前
before jerry has you for breakfast
让我们在一个简单的课程中将鸡带到鹰头鹰
let's bring chicken to shite hawk in one easy lesson
你收到我了吗，你好，兔子队长读了三个答案
are you receiving me hello rabbit leader read three answering
大声而清晰地接受你，我会尽力让你流泪，我要你
receiving you loud and clear right i'll try and get on your tear and i want you
采取回避行动，您好，兔头红树
to take evasive action understood hello rabbit leader red tree
接听
answering
被理解
understood
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[掌声]
[Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
你好，兔子队长，我以为你可能会从太阳进来
hello rabbit leader i thought you might come in from the sun
不要以为不要只是看一眼寻找混蛋而从不飞
don't think don't just glance look search for the bastards and never fly in
一条直线，或者你是死鸭，所以现在让我们再试一次
a straight line or you're a dead duck so now let's try it again
[音乐]或换句话说，当心
[Music] or in other words beware of the hun in
出于自己最了解的原因的太阳
the sun who for reasons best known to himself
将他最近的袭击仅限于我们的航道车队
has confined his recent attacks to our channel convoys
但是，这不会永远持续下去，但是它给了我们一次拉动自己的机会
however this won't last forever but it has given us a chance to pull ourselves
一起训练像您这样的人作为战斗机控制员，您将
together and to train people like you now as fighter controllers you'll be
加入一个组织，感谢上司并没有仓促起来
joining an organization which thank the good lord was not rushed up hastily
昨天这将是我们脖子上的痛苦
yesterday it'll be our pain in the neck to the
敌人来时是我们的笑柄
enemy when he comes it's the joker up our sleeves
现在rdf链向我们显示了它们在哪里，信息已传递到组
now the rdf chain shows us where they are the information is passed to group
小组争夺必要的中队，您在部门级别指导我们的工作
group scrambles the necessary squadrons and you at sector level guide our chaps
到拦截已经过尝试和测试
to the interception it's been tried and tested
它的工作原理，所以如果你不好就不要怪系统
it works so don't blame the system if you're no good
现在显然这里有一个拉丁美洲团体将首当其冲
now clearly a latin group here will bear the brunt of the battle
因为那些在那里张贴的人会发现您的不适
as those of you who are posted there will find out to your discomfort
12组是我们的第二道防线，涵盖了
12 group is our second line of defense and covers the industrial midlands of
北13组苏格兰和东北北部
the north 13 group scotland and the north east and
英格兰西部的10个小组的战斗机指挥力超过一半
10 group the west of england more than half of fighter command
中队在诅咒附近的第11组驻守，我们期望
squadrons are stationed here at 11 group near the curse where we expect the
入侵并能够保护伦敦，这是轰炸机可以得到的
invasion and also able to protect london which is as far as the bombers can get
与战斗机护送，但我认为我们可以将策略留给
with fighter escort but i think we can leave strategy to
那些戴着帽子的鸡蛋的人
those with egg on their hats
在这里谢谢你
here thank you
外国的
foreign
这个延误是我不可思议的运气
this delay is an incredible piece of luck i mean
他们卷起法国然后停下来，他们本来可以就知道的
they roll up france and then stop they could have come right on you know
最新情报是，希特勒在法国观光
latest intelligence is that hair hitler is sightseeing in france
天气比较宜人哦，我的意思是
there's rather pleasant weather oh i mean it
他在度假，我不是在抱怨部长
he's on holiday i'm not complaining minister
不，不，不，认真的爸爸，士气因素至关重要
no no no seriously daddy the morale factor is vital
我看到星期一星期一海狸坏了，他现在可以分娩了
i saw beaver broken on monday now he's going to be able to deliver
见到你之后，每周多达一百名战士我希望
as many as a hundred fighters a week well after seeing you i want to be able
回到内阁，告诉他们
to go back to the cabinet and tell them that
你对我一样有信心我知道
that you're as confident as i am damn it man we've got
650架飞机，那里有2500架飞机
650 planes and they have 2 500 aircraft isn't there
我们有雷达防喷罩，对雷达充满信心
and we have radar jet shield puts great faith in radar
这很重要，但不会击落飞机
and it's vital but it won't shoot down aircraft
我必须说你没有完全散发出乐观的精神
i must say you don't exactly exude a spirit of optimism
上帝愿意，我们将支持部长，我明白了，所以我告诉内阁，你是
god willing we will hold out minister i see so i tell the cabinet that you're
相信雷达并向上帝祈祷是正确的
trusting in radar and praying to god is that right
我准确地说是反过来，我相信上帝并为雷达祈祷
i accurate the other way around i'm trusting in god and praying for radar
但是最重​​要的算术是我们的年轻人
but the essential arithmetic is that our young men
将不得不以四比一的比率击落他们的年轻人
will have to shoot down their young men at the rate of four to one
如果我们要跟上一切
if we're to keep pace at all
是油压检查仪表
it's the oil pressure service the gauge is being checked
好的，查理继续进行，谢谢先生，永不放弃，你查理吗
all right charlie carry on thank you sir never give up do you charlie
仪器检查先生，我希望您的uco相信您
instrument check sir i hope your uco believes you
他现在会成为您头疼的问题之一哦，他们知道订单不会缠结
he's gonna be one of your headaches now oh they know the orders don't tangle
不必要，所以我可以做一个发动机检查先生或底切
unnecessarily so it's uh may i do an engine check sir or undercut
检查或广播借口使杰瑞斯很好
check or radio any excuse to get the jerrys well at
至少表明他们很热衷，是个好人，上帝知道
least it shows they're keen yeah they're a good bunch god knows what
我在苏格兰发现很多孩子脸颊都不好
i find in scotland a lot of kids with down on their cheeks
是的，训练他们成为战斗机飞行员真是比战斗更狡猾
yeah training them to be fighter pilots is a damn sight more dodgy than fighting
德国人好，你必须赢得新的条纹
germans well you've got to earn that new stripe
至少我在镇上呆了三天
somehow well at least i got three days in town
向您的妻子致以我的谢意
give my regards to your wife thanks
请问先生
may i have a word sir
祝你好运，谢谢你的聚会，兄弟，嘿，给我们寄回了羊杂粮
good luck thanks for the party bro hey send us back a haggis
[音乐]如果您想获得试飞许可
[Music] if you want permission for a test flight
答案是不
the answer is no
所以
so
呃，苏格兰威士忌，先生，请你走那么远
large uh scotch please you were that lot down the road sir
嗯，请不要六分之一
um no one in six please
啊
ah
您申请了苏格兰亲爱的那个职位，我不能
you applied for that post in scotland darling i can't
你知道我不能你的意思是你不想要它不能
you know i can't you mean you don't want it can't
我有一份工作，我们得到了什么，这到底是什么
i've got a job what have we got what the hell is this
出于上帝的缘故，这是婚姻还是火红的空军委员会？科林
is it a marriage or a flaming air force committee for god's sake colin don't
重新开始
start that all over again
我知道这会发生，你知道我从来不想你加入
i knew this would happen you know i never wanted you to join up never
打电话给你一点点的注意尝试表现
calling you take a blind bit of notice try to behave
好像我是一个人，你看起来更像一个阅兵场
as if i were a human being you look more like a parade ground
对我来说，我只是没有割草
suffragette to me i've just not cut out to wave a wet
出于上帝的缘故，在乌黑站上请你
hanky on [ __ ] station for god's sake who's asking you to
在一起在苏格兰哦，我永远受不了看着女人
be in scotland together oh i never could stand watching women
你不在乎我可以照顾我到这里50英里吗
you couldn't care less could you i cared enough to come here 50 miles
我没有测量
i didn't measure it i did
我什至预订了一个房间
i even booked a room
三天
three days
会很棒[音乐]
would be marvelous [Music]
你要申请那个职位还是不正确
are you going to apply for that posting or not right
左右左右左右正方形出
left right left right left right square out
右转
right turn
哦，磅，现在等一下
oh pounds now wait for it squad
是的
yes
[音乐]
[Music]
快来吧，阿尔伯特，您还没有死，但是
come on albert you're not dead yet it's
让他得到自己的
let him get his own
不，先生，这不是查理，很可能是果汁中的飓风
no sir it's not charlie some hurricane out of juice very likely
好吧，直接给我打电话，你会听到
right well call me directly you hear
任何事物
anything
好吧，一定有人发现他，他不能消失
well somebody must have spotted him he can't just disappear
好吧，我挂上先生，这是他们的声音武术公园
all right i'll hang on sir it's their voice martial park
这就是我们现在所需要的，紧紧抓住这个
that's all we need now jeremy hang on to this
下午好先生告诉你的男人放松
good afternoon sir tell your men to relax
他们是如何把坎菲尔德中队的一半编成新飞行员的
how are they making out canfield half the squadron the new pilot sir
这就是为什么您被派到这里让他们成型的原因，他们得到的警告更少
that's why you were sent here to let them into shape they get less warning
在这里比其他任何车站都要多，所以他们必须学会两分钟从待机中起床
here than any other station so they must learn to get up from standby in two
如果要拦截敌人，则要等几分钟
minutes flat if they're to intercept the enemy
你好分散
hello dispersal
右站下来飞行
right stand down a flight
当然是，先生，小伙子们宠坏了，嗯，坎菲尔德
of course yes sir the chaps spoil huh all right canfield
怎么了，你有一个飞行员失踪了，先生
what's up you have a pilot missing yes sir
在通道上
over the channel
他两个多小时就该还了吗？我以为我已经说清楚了我们也是
is he much overdue over two hours i thought i'd made it clear we're too
靠近敌人，让飞行员独自一人四处游荡
near the enemy for pilots to go swanning around on their own we can't afford to
这样失去他们这次的借口是什么
lose them this way what's the excuse this time
底盘检查工具，我们都做到了，但这就是
undercarriage check instruments we've all done it but that's
不好意思，他叫飞行员兰伯特
no excuse what's his name pilot officer lambert
[音乐]
[Music]
是[音乐]
be [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
[音乐]
[Music]
区
zone
让我们开始吧[音乐]
let's get started [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
[笑声] [音乐]
[Laughter] [Music]
[音乐]外国
[Music] foreign
[音乐]
[Music]
这些
these
[音乐]
[Music]
敌对的两三三早晨哦，承受一八六射程
hostile two three morning oh bearing one eight six range
三十英里二十加高六千是丹·摩尔我
thirty miles twenty plus height six thousand yes dan moore i
确认不当
confirm no iff
敌对的二九现在三十加是演示我确认
hostile two nine now thirty plus yes demo i confirm
重新检查，如果请芬太尼
recheck iff please fentanyl
很抱歉打电话给先生，但有东西在建是谢谢中心
sorry to call you in sir but something's building yeah thank you center
现在有两个八点四十多岁，对男孩有敌意
two eight now forty plus hostile come on boys
直到今晚都没有
none due through until tonight sir
敌对的三一四十五五更好地使更多中队待命
hostile three one forty five six better bring more squadrons to standby
好的，先生，请给我一个大山坡，再确认一下敌意2-3
all right sir give me a big hill reconfirm hostile 2-3
敌对2-3 1-8-0再次受到干扰，先生
hostile 2-3 1-8-0 getting interference again sir
现在不是下士现在不是5英里更好恐怕袭击是
not now corporal not now that's better five miles i'm afraid the raid is
进入我的地雷
entering my ground ray stan more
[音乐]
[Music]
佛塔[音乐]
stupas [Music]
[音乐]哦
[Music] oh
[音乐]
[Music]
让他们起来43个中队对斯坦·莫瑟（Stan morser）毫无敌意
get them up 43 squadrons hostile to one that was stan morser bent no radar out
行动
of action
谁在掩护多佛54中队
who's covering dover 54 squadron
[音乐]六个中队的机载太慢
[Music] six squadrons airbornes are too slow
他们中的一些人花了六到七分钟，他们必须在两分钟内完成
some of them took six and seven minutes they'll have to do it in two
她的天鹅绒领头人在左边的stukas roger那里，我们去了
her velvet leader down there on the left stukas roger here we go
正在攻击[音乐]
attacking now [Music]
黄色部分为伴您保持双眼皮
yellow section keep your eyes peeled for the escort
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]烈性人
[Music] spitfire
[音乐]啊
[Music] ah
[音乐]比谷仓门更容易打
[Music] easier to hit than a barn door it's like
在桶中射杀老鼠如果不注意，你会在桶中
shooting rats in a barrel you'll be in a barrel if you don't watch
为战士而战[音乐]
out for the fighters [Music]
河[音乐]
river [Music]
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
我们的地块干了，然后我们是盲人，所以现在我们只有观察员电话了
our plots are drying up then we're blind so now we've only got the observer call
这只是他们现在不会停止的开始
this is only the beginning they won't stop now
[音乐]
[Music]
脚踝
ankles
让我们把它加到一百以上
let's make it a hundred plus hello hello heinkels hundred plus
是的，中心仍然向北移动，高度为一万二千
yes center still going north height twelve thousand
分散的两个部分
dispersal two section scrambled
向右看
look out right
[音乐]
[Music]
哦
oh
[音乐]
[Music]
沃里克先生到处都能看到地图，就像猪圈一样
map can filth everywhere mr warwick it's like a pigsty
直到六点钟，厨师们才来，好吧，你有一些违约者
the cooks don't come on till six ah well you've got some defaulters
把它们放到上面就可以了，无论如何你都会足够快地进入那里
put them onto it come on you lot move you'll be in there fast enough anyways
真实的
real
我的天啊
oh my god
萨哈比节
section of sahabi
先生，警务人员业余爱好，我注意到您的某些女孩正在使用
sir section officer hobby i've noticed that some of your girls are now using
练习时的男子战es
the men's trenches during airaid practice
必须停止先生，另外还有防毒面具，如果他们是防毒面具的话
it's got to stop sir and another thing gas mask cases they're for gas masks
他们不是手提包，我当然意识到那个女性
they're not handbags i do realize of course that female
要求与邮件有所不同
requirements differ somewhat from the mail
尽管如此，这不是借口
nevertheless that's no excuse
上帝的牙齿
god's teeth
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]这样
[Music] so
[音乐]
[Music]
你通过了
you passed
[音乐]至少我们知道杰里要干什么
[Music] at least we know what jerry's going for
不幸的是，我们所有的机场[音乐]
all our airfields unfortunately [Music]
这是一个中队，先生，不要弄湿
it's a squadron scramble sir don't be wet
给我值班主任哦，他们刚刚下来
get me the duty controller oh they've just come down
我们仍在加油杀死控制
we're still refueling kill control
不要只是站在那里站起来
don't just stand there get one up
在20年代
in the 20s
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]这样
[Music] so
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
[音乐]
[Music]
所以[音乐]
so [Music]
谈论有毛的起飞，我看到吉米买了
talk about a hairy takeoff i saw jimmy buy it
阿奇下车了吗？哦，我和你在一起，但我已经把肚子丢了
did archie get off oh i'm with you old boy but i've left my stomach behind
我闭嘴，你会把兔子领头交给考斯科夫吗？
i shut up will you rabbit leader to cowslip control do you
读我为基督的缘故醒来会
read me over for christ's sake wake up will
机载兔中队
rabbit squadron airborne
关闭红色两个
close up red two
现在在您向东20英里处
and it's now 20 miles east of you heading
东南
south east
现在[音乐]
now [Music]
你到底在哪里
where the hell are you
西蒙，你到底在哪里[音乐]
where the hell are you simon [Music]
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
哦
oh
[音乐]
[Music]
团结起来
pull yourself together
呆在西摩
stay with seymour
没关系
that's all right
[音乐]这样
[Music] so
[音乐]
[Music]
把那支香烟熄灭，电源消失了
put that cigarette out the mains are gone
不能这样做气[音乐]
can't do so gas [Music]
你不骂我沃里克先生吗
don't you yell at me mr warwick
是的，人类在那里向下看着你更高
yeah human down down there looking at it you higher
[掌声]
[Applause]
给我一些舒展，命令妈妈现在可以让一些女孩站下来
give me some stretches and the order mom can stand some of the girls down now
琼斯·惠特曼下士清理那烂摊子，然后你可以花五分钟
corporal jones whitman clear up that mess then you can take five minutes yes
43站了下来，一对一释放501在唐熊那里倒下
43 stand down one one one released 501 are down at tang bear they couldn't
像这样再过几天，我们就不会大发脾气
get in at big in a few more days like this and we won't
能够将它们放倒在任何地方，我想我们总能把它们全部拉下来
be able to get them down anywhere i suppose we can always pull them all
回到泰晤士河以北超出范围，这正是他们希望我们采取的行动
back north of the thames out of range that is precisely what they want us to
[音乐]做
[Music] do
[音乐]
[Music]
这是英国广播公司的上门服务，这是九点钟的新闻
this is the bbc home service here is the nine o'clock news
今天，大型敌机编队袭击了英格兰南部的目标
large formations of enemy aircraft today attacked targets in southern england
但是敌人的空中舰队受到了严厉的惩罚
but the enemy's aerial armada came in for heavy punishment
我们只有15架飞机中的最后一架摧毁了47架德国飞机
over 47 german planes were destroyed for the last of only 15 of our own aircraft
其中六名飞行员被救出，数架空军机场也遭到袭击
six of these pilots were saved several raf aerodromes were also attacked
一些人员伤亡得以维持，但轻伤
and some casualties were sustained but they were light
[音乐]
[Music]
污垢
dirt
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐是
[Music] is
[音乐]
[Music]
嗯
uh
帮助自己，每个人都没有战斗机护航
help yourself everybody there's no fighter escort
[音乐]
[Music]
别
don't
[音乐]
[Music]
肥皂盒的负责人将其从家里和茶中拿出来，但是一旦您配得上很好
soapbox leader break it off home and tea but once you deserve it well done
大家
everybody
[音乐]
[Music]
脚踝三秒爆破右舷发动机
ankle three second burst starboard engine
非常棒的喷火器，机翼上有任何识别标记或黄色条纹
very great flamer any identification marks yellow stripes on the wings or
联队领导人看到它降下来了吗
wing leader see it go down did i yeah
很好，格雷厄姆和乔科可以改变你的故事
plonk hmm well graham and jocko can turn your story
那是你们三个让他嘿嘿，杀死一个小伙子三分之一
that's three of you got him hey a third of a kill laddie a third
先生
sir
嗯，任何人似乎要进去的海因克尔的喜悦，都不知道你和我们在一起
well any joy a heinkel anyone seemed to go in didn't know you were with us
彼得做得好
well done peter
先生的只有三分之一哦，总比没有好
only a third of a one sir oh that's better than nothing
我曾经爆炸过，从来没有碰过香肠
i used to blast away and never hit a sausage
一件事是什么，先生，这需要我们
one thing though what's that sir it takes us uh
两年来训练像您这样的人假设您的控件已损坏
two years to train people like you suppose your controls have been damaged
你本来那愚蠢的胜利榜会发生什么
what would have happened to that idiotic victory roll of yours you'd have been
散布在该死的感觉像草莓酱
spread all over the damn feel like strawberry jam
再也不会清楚听
never again clear listen
克利夫兰，他的日子过得还不错，老人刚下楼，
cleveland something to make stuff his day well the old man's just gone down to
行动室里，诺顿突袭行动的刺杀最终数字23
the ops room with sasser final figures of the norton raids 23
没有损失，快活，好，没错
without loss jolly good that's it right
我们从沿海司令部和机队空中得到了六名志愿飞行员
we're getting six volunteer pilots from coastal command and from the fleet air
从每个童话之战中回答五个
answer five from each of the fairy battle
中队与三军合作
squadrons and three from army cooperation
那是30岁吗我们昨天失去了那么多的空气吗？
it's uh 30 is it not enough ever we lost that many yesterday and the air
工作人员犹豫要削弱轻型轰炸机，以防万一
staff hesitate to weaken the light bombers in case
入侵，所以我们现在需要飞行员，下属的外国中队怎么办
of invasion so we need pilots now what about the foreign squadrons under
捷克两极的训练是的，我知道您对
trainings of czech's poles yes i know your feelings about the
语言上的困难，呃，他们听不懂他们说的话
language difficulty uh they don't understand a word that's said to them
在那边他们对自己和我们都是一种威胁
over there they're a menace to themselves and us
我会尽力减少培训计划的难度
i'll try and cut some more corners off the training program
飞行员做得很好，敌人以二比一的速度失败
pilots are doing well enemy losing at the rate of two to one
那么他负担不起，他永远不会一次发射超过一半的轰炸机
then he can afford to can't he never sends more than half his bombers at one
时间必须找到鲍勃飞行员
time must find bob pilots
或输掉[音乐]
or lose [Music]
开始这是关闭速度检查fiverr准备就绪
begin this is off speed check fiverr one back of readiness
我想你会看到这位先生，谢谢
i think you'll see this sir thank you
艾滋病预警部门3
airaid warning sector 3
红色[音乐]
red [Music]
我们将后部右舷变黄，而将木板取下
we'll take the rear starboard yellow you take the board
黄色wilco tally黄色
yellow one wilco tally hoe yellow
剩下的很多人都睁大了眼睛
and a lot of you keep your eyes open for the rest score
[音乐]
[Music]
[掌声]
[Applause]
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
爬
climb
[音乐]
[Music]
[掌声]
[Applause]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
在你的能量背后
behind your energy
[掌声]
[Applause]
跳出糖果跳
get out candy jump
[音乐]绳
[Music] rope
[音乐]
[Music]
外部
outside
你们大家杰里的谈话英语下士
don't any of you jerry's talk english corporal
先生，您在哪里，把那些秃ul人员带到西部，把教堂带到
sir where are you taking those vultures officers to the west and church to the
天啊，先生，地狱，你对他们负责
god room sir like hell you are they're responsible for all that get them to
清理一下，但是军官给什么呢
clear it up but what about the officers sir give
他们一把血淋淋的铲子来了
them a bloody shovel come on
船长讨厌杰里，如果不修理那把枪，你会讨厌我
skipper hates jerry's you'll hate me if you don't get that gun repaired
然后收起这个小锁
then wrap up this little lock
早上只有八点比那场飞行要好，五个是
only eight for the morning gotta do better than that flight well five are
冲销一个有另一辆车走了，两个是
write-offs one has another car gone and two are
思念安东尼先生和摩尔警长
missing sir mr anthony and sergeant moore
这两个是100小时的检查，他们已经坚持48小时了
these two are 100 hour checks they've been at it for 48 hours solid
先生，我知道
sir i know
你到底在哪里学游泳
where the hell have you been learning to swim
做你最好的飞罗杰，你得到一个我得到的只是肚子
do your best fly roger did you get one all i got was a belly
充满英语频道，你什么时候学
full of english channel when are you gonna learn
我不知道他们在那里从来不会直飞超过30级
i didn't know they were there never fly straight and level for more than 30
在战斗区域的几秒钟我告诉过你多少次
seconds in the combat area how many times have i told you come
上，我给你搭便车，我宁愿走，先生，剪掉这个
on i'll give you a lift i'd rather walk sir cut out this
嗯
uh
你打电话给你老婆
you called your wife
好男孩进来[音乐]
all right boy get in [Music]
[音乐]嘿，怎么了，谢谢
[Music] hey what's up thank you
荒谬的是，我们每天要爬四到五次，每次下来
it's ridiculous we go up four or five times a day and every time we come down
更多的坑洞，然后更多的坑洞，直到我们不能
more pothole and then more potholes until we can't
血腥的我们进了门，我们将再次使这个地方运转
bloody we'll get in a door we'll get this place operational again
直到有人决定保护我们时，您才会这样做
you won't not until someone decides to protect it while we're up
[音乐]
[Music]
炽热的天才想到了将我们送往飞行俱乐部的那个垃圾场的想法
what flaming genius thought of sending us to that dump of a flying club
别怪我导演们停泊自己，这不是一个糟糕的小领域，我见过
don't blame me directors park himself it's not a bad little field i've seen it
潮湿的帐篷，一个充满死蝇的讨厌的小棚屋
damp tent a nasty little shack full of dead flies
好吧，至少你不会有果冻来拜访你，我不怪他们
well at least you won't have the jellies visiting you i don't blame them
[音乐]
[Music]
[鼓掌]引擎的运作时间
[Applause] how much longer ops the engine's
过热，所以我是要么站下来要么炸毁
overheating and so am i we either stand down or blow up which do
你要
you want
[音乐]敌对一六我们确认需要
[Music] hostile one six we confirm please need
今晚还有更多黄色七人制，现在两个九点四十加一
some more yellow sevens tonight style two nine now forty plus one
五
five
是的两个六和四个一个细节要拦截
yes two six and four one detail to intercept
七个中队空降先生，谢谢，让我们现在来分组
seven squadrons airborne sir thank you let's draw group now
并确保他们知道当我们起床时他们正在保护我的飞机场
and make sure they know they're protecting my airfields while we're up
他们被告知先生，再告诉他们强大的领袖
they have been told sir tell them again mighty leader
这是火鸡控制vector192我在麦德斯通上为您交易
this is turkey control vector192 i have some trade for you over maidstone
土耳其控制松树领袖罗杰190。
turkey control pine tree leader roger 190. finally
这是火鸡20加匪在天使2-0向西行驶时
this is turkey 20 plus bandits at angels 2-0 heading west
罗杰火鸡控制[音乐]
roger turkey control [Music]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
是[音乐]
is [Music]
休息[音乐]
break [Music]
[掌声]
[Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
在你的尾巴杰米
on your tail jamie
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
嗯
uh
[音乐]
[Music]
敌机逼近先生，直奔我们
enemy aircraft approaching sir coming straight for us
现在五点20加上大约800英尺
20 plus about 800 feet now at five
[音乐]
[Music]
[该死的笑声]永远不会
[Laughter] that should damn will never have
发生在地狱是12组他们被要求的先生
happened where the hell is 12 group they were requested sir
好吧，他们永远不会发现他们认为自己是魔鬼
well they're never in sight find out what the devil they think they're
在玩
playing at
[音乐]他们只是落在我们身上得到了我的电话号码
[Music] they just fell on us they got my number
两个，你看到坎菲尔德摔倒了
two and they you saw canfield go down
它炸了就炸了
it blew up just blew out
就像我们认为的那样糟糕，这再次激起了混乱，其余的
as bad as we thought it was kindly invigorate shambles again and the rest
不会更好，上帝知道我们将拥有多少架飞机
is not much better god knows how many aircraft we'll have
早上都是因为高个子组没做他们的事
in the morning all because tall group didn't do their stuff
李·马洛里（Lee Mallory）和他所谓的大翅膀不妨留给所有人
lee mallory and his so-called big wings might as well stay on the ground for all
使用他们是我们起来先生试图敲掉
the use they are we were up sir trying to knock out the
敌我们的群众，但需要时间来组装
enemy our mass but it takes time to assemble
15,000英尺处的40或50架飞机需要花费很长时间
40 or 50 aircraft at 15 000 feet it takes far
到您的大翼飞起来的时候，敌人已经击中了目标，
too long by the time your big wing is up the enemy have hit their targets and are
在他们回家的路上，最重要的是击落他们
on their way home all that matters is to shoot them down
我宁愿在他们被击中后销毁50个
in large numbers i'd rather destroy 50 after they've hit
他们的目标比之前的10个要好
their targets than 10 before don't forget the target's on my airfield
马洛里，你甚至不到50
mallory and you're not getting 50 or not even
变得10.先生们，您错过了基本道理
getting 10. gentlemen you're missing the essential truth
我们缺少200名飞行员，我们已经疲惫不堪
we are short of 200 pilots those we have are tired strained
为了救济我们正在为生存而战
and all over due for relief we're fighting for survival
输了
losing
我们不需要大翼或小翼，我们需要飞行员
we don't need a big wing or a small wing we need pilots
和一个奇迹般的晚安先生们
and a miracle goodnight gentlemen
晚安晚安先生
good night good night sir
现在到伦敦萨沃伊饭店欣赏舞蹈音乐，直到与
and now over to the savoy hotel london for dance music until midnight with
卡罗尔·吉本斯和他的萨伏伊饭店
carol gibbons and his savoy hotel
[音乐]
[Music]
奥菲斯
orpheus
我要说的是，穿制服看起来更好
i'm gonna say you look a damn sight better out of uniform
哈雷记得你不在你身边，那是谁的错
harley remember you out of yours and whose fault's that
哦，为了上帝的缘故，不要再该死了，我的中队南下，你只需要申请
oh for god's sake not again look damn it my squadron's come south you just apply
对于那个张贴科林没有好吧好吧同意禁忌
for that posting colin no all right all right agree taboo
今晚受
subject tonight
不要笑
no laughs
你真的以为我们郑重地去穿这些荒谬的衣服
you really think we're uh solemnly going to get into these ridiculous garments
肯定不在这个阶段
not at this stage surely
我确定哦，玛吉，来吧，这只是
i'm sure oh maggie come on it's just
我很害羞
i am shy
老实说[音乐]
honestly [Music]
患病的
i'll
不，不只是床，是我们，是你
no it's not just bed it's us it's you
[音乐]
[Music]
我
me
听我说
hear me
哦好
oh good
呼叫者
caller
承诺
promise
是的，他们是炸弹，他们是在炸弹伦敦，该死的也太近了
yes they're bombs they're bombing london too damn close
[音乐]
[Music]
谢谢你[音乐]
thank you [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
是
is
这里
here
[音乐]嗯
[Music] um
[音乐]嘿
[Music] hey
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]通过
[Music] via
是
be
外国的
foreign
[鼓掌] [笑声]
[Applause] [Laughter]
[掌声]
[Applause]
外国的
foreign
[掌声]
[Applause]
外国的
foreign
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
下午
afternoon
[音乐]这样
[Music] so
[音乐]
[Music]
所以
so
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
[音乐]
[Music]
是
is
[音乐]
[Music]
是
is
[音乐]
[Music]
嘿
hey
[音乐]
[Music]
兔子领袖矢量160土匪100加
rabbit leader vector 160 bandits 100 plus
天使五分之一弯曲超过100
angels one five bend its 100 plus over
抓住它到箭头我看不到他们，但他们必须在那里好起来，
grab it to arrow i can't see them but they must be there well come up and
寻找自己，什么也没有，我什么也没重复
look for yourself there nothing i repeat nothing group please
是的
yes
我们所拥有的一切并使他们动起来他们这次抓住了我们
everything we've got and get them moving they've caught us this time
他们正在向西北转，好像是伦敦，现在是伦敦
they're turning north west it looks like london it's london all right
而且我们已经涵盖了飞机场的一切
and we've got everything up covering airfields
[音乐]
[Music]
发声皇家空军
voice the royal air force
[音乐]
[Music]
所以
so
史密斯先生，我不酷先生
mr smith i ain't cool mr smees
失利
loss
[音乐]
[Music]
压力又在下降
the pressure's dropping again
外国的
foreign
这是我所能带领的
this is as far as i can get led
买那辆车
buy that car
嘿，不，你不是什么意思，那儿有一千磅
hey no you don't what do you mean there's a thousand pounder down there
如果您正在寻找某人，它现在还没有消失
and it's not gone off now if you're looking for somebody
他们都在教堂里
they're all down there at the church all
[音乐]
[Music]
他将不得不喝那只红狮子，那里不会有他
he'll have to drink the red lion there won't he still have him
哦，该死的傻瓜，你能不能让我度过半休假，看看你们都在保存
oh bloody stupid can you get i spent half a leave seeing you all saving the
国家，你把他带回了所有这一切，对不起，这只是
country you bring him back to all this i'm sorry it's just
我们想念每个人，你们都回去了，爸爸，你完成了吗？
we missed everyone you're all going back dad have you finished it have you got it
在岸边的街上有一个家庭，我们可以再招募一些志愿者吗
there's a family trapped in shore street can we have some more volunteers
[音乐]
[Music]
我会回来的
i'll be back though
[音乐]停止那该死的钟声
[Music] stop that bloody bell
还可以从后面
okay more from the back
不是真正的烈性烈火，他们无法在这里降落
not real spitfires they couldn't land here
一分钟后，您会看到只有警官飞喷火
you'll see in a minute only officers fly spitfires
你不是战斗机飞行员你的顶部按钮怎么样
you're not a fighter pilot what about your top button
任何人都可以做到这一点[音乐]
anybody can do that [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
你
you
嗯
um
有
there's
所以
so
t5极地训练中队是什么
t5 what's that a training squadron sir the poles
让他们摆脱困境
get them out of it get them down
黑步行领袖矢量2 3 0并立即返回基地
black walk leader vector 2 3 0 and return to base immediately over
黑鹰领袖收到并了解
black hawk leader received and understood out
黑鹰队首领飞往港口并操纵两个
black hawk leader to a flight turn to port and steer two
三零克星
three zero nemesis
停止波兰语的ter不休，转向两个三零
stop that polish chatter and steer two three zero
重复一次，我再说两个三零
repeat this i say again two three zero please
但是大声喊叫两个也许三个零
but crying out loud two maybe three zero
再说一遍，现在请闭嘴，跟随我
repeat please now just shut up a lot of you and follow me
除非你是盲人
unless you're blind as well as
哦天哪[音乐]
oh god [Music]
波兰语
in polish
[音乐]
[Music]
一个raf不是马戏团
one the raf is not a flying circus
始终遵守两个严格的rt程序
two strict rt procedure will be observed at all times
用于私人抛光
for private polish
终于，只有上帝知道我为什么收到以下信号
finally and god alone knows why i've received the following signal
恭喜，今天这个中队是
congratulations as of today this squadron is
签署了基思公园空军行动副马歇尔AOC 11集团的业务
operational signed keith park air vice marshall aoc 11 group
[音乐]
[Music]
我对民意调查错了，我们还有第二个波兰中队长
i was wrong about the polls we also have the second polish squadron sir
我以为你会提到它们好使它们运作
i thought you'd mention them all right make them operational
加拿大人和支票我们都需要
and the canadians and the checks we need them all
看起来又像伦敦先生，是的，我们对此无能为力
looks like london again sir yes and there's nothing we can do about it
但是如果女孩要白天集中精力在伦敦
but if girling should concentrate on london by day
这是另一回事，是否意味着他独自离开我的机场
it's another matter if it means he leaves my airfields alone
我什至会抱怨几天会给我恢复到饱的机会
i shall complain even a few days would give me the chance to get back to full
力量足够的父亲来回去
strength enough father to come and go back
我们将有更多时间来拦截更重要的公园
we'll have more time to intercept what's more important park
他的战士在伦敦只加油了十分钟
his fighters have only fueled enough for 10 minutes over london
轰炸机将首次失去大部分保护
bombers will lose much of their protection for the first time
他们全都在12名乘员范围内
they'll all come within the range of 12 crew
也许现在终于可以看到李·马洛里的大翅膀是由什么制成的
perhaps now at last we shall see what lee mallory's big wings are made of
开启伦敦可能是德国最大的失误
turning on london could be the german's biggest blunder
[音乐]蜘蛛队长这是礼帽控制
[Music] spider leader this is top hat control
现在在您以东20英里处，向东南行驶
and it's now 20 miles east of you heading south east
矢量一二零使天使二哦
vector one two zero make angel two oh
罗杰礼帽领袖，这是探戈控制
roger top hat leader this is tango control
[音乐]控制您的客户似乎
[Music] control your customers appear to be
拆分前往伦敦的主力部队将是
splitting up main force heading for london will be
您的目标向量零九零
your target vector zero nine zero
罗杰顶级蝙蝠侠控制爬上天使
roger top batman control climb to angels
一九罗杰蝙蝠侠
one nine roger batman
再次谢谢你的车道
thank you again lane
这应该给他们一些思考
this should give them something to think about
尾灯采用星光控制，留意与您同在的友好机翼
starlight control to dog tail keep an eye out for a friendly wing joining you
在你左舷的罗杰星光下，我看见他
on your port side roger starlight i see him
我看到他血腥奇妙的狐步舞领袖探戈控制，这是
i see him bloody marvelous foxtrot leader tango control and it's
现在可能略低于你，罗杰·探戈，我有他们
now probably slightly below you roger tango i've got them
peewee领袖现在转爆炸形
peewee leader turning starburst now
当心109是关于罗杰·费尔菲尔德队长
watch out for 109 is about roger fairfield leader
现在上升，以左手双蓝领队罗杰其他所有人继续
going up now take the left-hand pair blue leader roger everybody else keep
绑
tied
[音乐]
[Music]
大家安静
everyone keep quiet
[音乐]
[Music]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
离开燃烧的战斗机，这是我们想要的血腥轰炸机
leave the flaming fighters it's the bloody bombers we want
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
在你后面
behind you
[掌声]
[Applause]
下午好，下午好，我的屁股，你的混蛋把你的优势挺过来
good afternoon good afternoon my ass you bosh bastard put your edge up come
把它们放上去等等
on put them up go blah blah
[音乐]
[Music]
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
乐趣
fun
烈性人[音乐]
spitfire [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
外国的
foreign
[音乐是
[Music] is
[音乐]
[Music]
罗杰[掌声]
roger [Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
[掌声]
[Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
所以
so
非常感谢老兄
thanks awfully old chap
好吧你
all right you
[音乐]外国
[Music] foreign
我们应该在被炸毁之前搬进这里啊，玛吉
we should have moved in here before we were bombed ah maggie
我想请您认识我们新的助理控制小队长汤姆·埃文斯（Tom Evans）
i'd like you to meet our new assistant controller squad leader tom evans
科长哈维
section officer harvey
你好吗，他认识你的老人
how'd you do hello he knows your old man
自从我小小的飓风肆虐以来，科林怎么还没见过他
how is colin i haven't seen him since my little escapade with a burning hurricane
对不起，妈妈，妈妈打个电话给你，请问
excuse me ma'am mom there's a call for you will you excuse
我一分钟，是的，谢谢
me just a minute yes thanks
你好，我到底是怎么穿过这里的哦
hello me how on earth did you get through here oh
放下抹布我说我不是空中的战斧
put it down to rag i said i was no battle axe from the air
部
ministry
关于您发布愚蠢的傻瓜消息的消息真是太聪明了
that was very clever any news about you're posting you silly idiot
好吧，您已经申请了我，我在这里一直很忙，实际上并不是所有的事情都那么简单
well you've applied i i've been so busy here it's really not as simple as all
现在看来为什么不该死
that now look why the hell not well to be
绝对诚实，我忘了我知道，亲爱的，我很抱歉看组
absolutely honest i forgot i know darling i'm sorry look group is
现在在这里，我马上去和他说话
here now i'll go and talk to him right away
没事吧
all right got it
科林
colin colin
打通好先生
get through all right sir yes
我给你个忠告那是什么意思
let me give you a piece of advice what's that said
保持单身
stay single
你还和我在一起吗狗尾巴红色两个肯定的红色领袖
are you still with me dog tail red two affirmative red leader
稍微落后于您，位于您的右舷
slightly behind you and on your starboard side
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
他拿到109发生了什么事然后遇到麻烦，但他没事
what happened to he got a 109 then ran into trouble but he's all right
没错，我看到他纾困了
no mistake i saw him bail out
正确的标准将详细介绍您的各种
right standardies here will detail you to your various
手表
watches
我忽略了一些关于狼哨声的知识
i left out the bit about the wolf whistles you're better at that the irks
时至今日，他们还在想其他事情
have other things on their minds nowadays thank goodness
再见肖恩
bye sean
是科林，他不是玛格死人[音乐]
it's colin he isn't dead maggie [Music]
会没事的
going to be all right
他们如今可以创造奇迹，您知道这只是时间问题
they can do wonders nowadays you know it's just a question of time that's all
忘记您的帖子，这样您就可以靠近他
forget your posting so you can be near him
他被严重烧死了吗[音乐]
is he badly burned [Music]
你送给我的先生，彼得，我要你接管红色部分
you sent for me sir yes peter i want you to take over red section
我是谁，二号和三号先生，有几个新伙计们
who am i numbers two and three sir there are a couple of new lads
他们在外面
they're outside
然后马上走
get moving right then
先生，这儿吐几个小时紧张
how many hours on spits tense here seven sir
像胶水一样粘在我身上，保持双眼
stick to me like glue and keep your eyes
打开
open
温斯顿会选择像这样的日期降落并进行翻新
winston would pick on a date like this to come landed and refurbished
龙虾储备的一切都没有吗
is everything up the lobster reserves no
我刚刚告诉总理，我确认了敌对的命运
that's what i've just told the prime minister i confirm hostile fortune
请求支持并请确认cultureshaw的项目
request to stand by and please confirm cultureshaw's project
空降
airborne
[音乐]红三这是红一更近我
[Music] red three this is red one much closer i
几乎看不到你
can hardly see you
红牙，你必须跟上我
red tooth you must keep up with me
右边的红色部分，我们像胶水一样粘在我身上
right red section here we go stick to me like glue
[音乐]红三在你身后
[Music] red three behind you
[鼓掌]所以
[Applause] so
[音乐]这样
[Music] so
[音乐]
[Music]
所以
so
蓝色
come in blue
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐]
[Music]
嘿，孩子们闭嘴，你是英国广播公司吗
hey kids shut up will you this is the bbc
上门服务是九点钟的新闻
home service here is the nine o'clock news
这是阿尔瓦拉多（Alvarado）直到今晚8点才读的书165
and this is alvarado reading it up till 8 o'clock tonight 165
德国飞机在敌人企图大规模袭击中被摧毁
german aircraft had been destroyed in big scale attacks attempted by the enemy
今天在伦敦和东南，我们迷路了
today on london and the southeast we lost
30名战士和10名飞行员安全
30 fighters with 10 of the pilots safe
白金汉宫再次遭到轰炸，但没人受伤
buckingham palace has been bombed again but no one was hurt
是的，是片刻的空姐先生，我是加扰者
yes yes one moment it's the air minister sir i'm the scrambler
是的，爸爸，呃，看起来我们华盛顿的人有
yes ah daddy uh look our people in washington are having
美国新闻界的麻烦，你知道这是关于今天的数字
trouble with the american press you know it's about today's figures
有德国消息人士说，我们的主张是疯狂的
german sources there are saying that our claims are wildly
夸张的
exaggerated
你好，爸爸在吗，我在这里，部长，我的意思是你
hello are you there daddy i'm here minister well i mean can you
核实我对宣传不太感兴趣的数字
verify the figures i'm not very interested in propaganda
如果我们是对的，他们会放弃；如果我们错了，他们将在一周内到达伦敦
if we're right they'll give up if we're wrong they'll be in london in a week
[掌声]
[Applause]
所以
so
滑动
slide
分散
dispersal
合适的奶酪
right cheese up
早上好先生
good morning sir morning
山姆，他们今天早上迟到了，这些混蛋在忙些什么
they're late this morning sam the bastards are up to something
[音乐]
[Music]
在我后面[音乐]
behind me [Music]
[音乐]
[Music]
做
do
[音乐]
[Music]
所以
so
[音乐]这样
[Music] so
[音乐]
[Music]
你
you